The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Late stage Core Formation ?
The Chaotic Broken Stars
can actually make copies of my body
with a higher cultivation than mine.
As expected,
it even replicated my artifacts.
Ancient God Restriction !
The Ji Realm is ineffective.
That means there is no consciousness to attack...
These things aren't alive.
The Ji Realm is useless,
they have the same artifacts as I do.
However,
this body reconstructed with the Ancient God's inheritance
cannot be copied by mere rocks !
My reconstructed Ancient God body is indeed strong
but it's still very far from what I saw in the memory inheritance.
No wonder those Soul Formation didn't force their way through this place.
It gets exponentially more difficult.
In the Land of the Ancient God
not only did I learn restrictions
but I also obtained this Ancient God body
and I obtained a Soul Core.
The Chaotic Broken Stars
can't stop me.
Now, I need to focus on forming a Nascent Soul
and then return to Zhao for vengeance.
Mo Yun\NQi Huang Sect disciple\NEarly stage Core Formation
Qian Kun\NPoison Devil Palace disciple\NMiddle stage Core Formation
Why did I flee here of all places...
You have nowhere left to run.
The Chaotic Broken Stars is famous in the Sea of Devils.
I’ve never heard of someone crossing it.
Don’t tell me you want to try ?
Senior,
Junior was lucky enough
to barely escape the Poison Demon Palace.
Why must you kill me ?
I'm merely following orders.
You should blame yourself for taking something you shouldn’t have !
This is something that belongs to my master !
Does it make a difference ?
It’s just a sect that was long destroyed.
You refuse to be the palace lord’s concubine
and foolishly stole the treasure furnace.
Don’t blame this old man for being ruthless !
Senior, if you continue
Junior will enter the Chaotic Broken Stars
and you'll leave empty-handed.
Senior,
this jade slip
contains the most pill recipes of the Qi Huang Sect.
It's as valuable as the furnace.
Will you let me go?
if I give you this jade slip ?
Fine,
give me the jade slip.
Once I confirm it’s real,
I’ll let you leave.
Please Senior, retreat 1000 zhang
and I’ll leave the jade slip here
after I leave.
Nonsense ! I don't have time to play games with you !
Senior, how could you break your word ?
Since you’re so sensible,
I’ll make sure you die comfortably !
That’s...
A person !?
How did he cross the Chaotic Broken Stars ?
I once saw a Nascent Soul Elder from the Poison Demon Palace
being anihilated by the Chaotic Broken Stars.
Even his Nascent Soul couldn’t escape...
What cultivation does this person have ?
Could he be Soul Formation ?
Junior Mo Yun of the Qi Huang Sect
pays respects to Senior.
Junior Qian Kun 5th-generation disciple of Poison Demon Palace
What’s the nearest city from here ?
Senior, 300 000 li west of here
is Qilin City.
Junior can guide you there.
As long as this person is here,
Qian Kun won’t dare to attack me.
Does Qilin City have Soul Formation cultivators ?
Of course not !
Senior, Qilin City doesn't have any Soul Formation cultivators.
Even among the 10 major cities of the Sea of Devils,
there are very few.
Ever since
several famous Soul Formation Devil Lords
disappeared within the Chaotic Broken Stars,
Soul Formation cultivators became a rare sight in the Sea of Devils.
Which Soul Formation cultivators
disappeared in this Chaotic Broken Stars ?
Senior,
200 years ago
Poison Devil City Lord, Meng Qingfan,
Devil Lord of Qi Mei City, Duanmu Ji,
the Xuan Tian Sect Leader, the Six Desires Devil Lord
and Ancient Emperor, Gu Di
all agreed to meet in the Chaotic Broken Stars
and vanished.
Their disciples
have been looking for them for 200 years
but didn't find a single clue.
I didn't think that 200 years would go by like that.
So Hunchback Meng was your Ancestor ?
This is bad...
The Ancestor went around the world
making countless enemies...
Judging by his attitude,
he must have a grudge with the Ancestor.
If the word spreads out that I walked out of the Chaotic Broken Stars,
trouble is bound to follow me.
Brat, don’t run !
Let Uncle Xu devour you
to repay Master's favor of letting me out again !
This...
This artifact is actually a Nascent Soul slave ?
With the Ancient God Tactic,
my body can absorb 80% of a Golden Core
and convert the remaining 20% to spiritual energy.
That's really impressive.
Senior,
Junior has a residence in Qilin City.
With Junior's status as a resident,
Senior
doesn't need to worry about anything.
This restriction activates every 3 days.
When it activated, your spiritual energy will be in chaos.
If I don't stop it within 15 minutes,
you'll instantly turn to a puddle of blood.
Don't try to pull any tricks.
Lead the way.
The legend says
that Qilin City already existed before the mist
Qilin City\NSea of Devils
of the Sea of Devils condensed.
It's one of the 10 major cities in the Sea of Devils.
Take me to your residence.
Jade token.
You can enter.
Senior,
Yun’er fell in love with you at first sight,
I’d never betray you.
Could you please lift this restriction ?
Don’t do anything unnecessary.
Junior... won’t dare !
I won’t stay in the Sea of Devils for too long.
I'll lift the restriction when I leave.
If you say anything about me coming out of the Chaotic Broken Stars,
don’t blame me for being ruthless.
Understood, Senior...
Once Tuo Sen leaves the Land of the Ancient God,
he will look for me for the memory inheritance.
I obtained quite a few artifacts in this trip.
No matter what,
I must quickly form my Nascent Soul.
These 9 artifacts
still have lingering Divine Sense
even if their owners are dead
so I can't use them.
This one might be worth a try.
Hurry up, leave !
With this artifact to help us,
Master is sure to form a Nascent Soul !
Master, are you going to kill that girl ?
Just ask me !
Shut up.
Nascent Soul is imminent.
Just to be safe,
I'll find the materials to refine a Restriction Flag.
Shopkeeper, I’ll take this.
Fellow cultivator has good taste !
She’s clearly plotting something.
Master, you must strike first.
Quickly send me to devour her !
Not yet.
I want to see
if anyone in Qilin City
can break my restriction.
Treasure Refining Pavilion
Master is an Enlightened of Restriction Mountain.
No one in this shabby city could possibly break it.
Fellow cultivator, take a look at our talismans and pills.
With Flood Dragon bones
the formation
will resist Core Formation cultivators for days.
The core has healing properties.
The marrow is even more precious, it's concentrated spiritual energy.
I took the liberty of crafting it
so that Senior may use it.
It's been 200 years...
I wonder where she is now...
Senior !
This hide was stripped from the Flood Dragon
right after its death.
The cultivator who skinned the dragon
was a famous Foundation Establishment cultivator
200 years ago in the outskirts of the Sea of Devils.
He had a breakthrough despite being chased by Core Formation cultivators  !
After he reached Core Formation,
he slaughtered all his pursuers
and he even forced a Middle stage Core Formation
to use the Hundred Days Execution Order !
Get me everything on this list.
Right away !
Senior,
can you really break the restriction ?
Come up,
I will break the restriction.
But you must tell me
who placed this restriction on you.
You might be wondering why Wang Lin says that he needs to focus on Nascent Soul when we weren't ever shown him advance further than Early stage Core Formation.\NThere are 2 breakthroughs in the novel during the Land of the Ancient God that weren't shown in the donghua.\N\NThe first one happens in episode 31 when Wang Lin took 7 years to learn restrictions and his hair turned white due to the stress. At that time, his cultivation naturally broke through to Middle stage Core Formation.\N\NThe second one happens in episode 34 when Wang Lin obtained the crystal of memory inheritance that the Sky Devil Magician condensed by killing the Six Desires Devil Lord. Right after that he hides for some time in the Heaven Defying Bead to cultivate and let some time pass because he was being chased. During that time he learns to use the Ancient God Tactic to devour Golden Cores he has in his bag of holding along with the pills Li Muwan made for him and he reached Late stage Core Formation.\N\NWhen he went back to find Ma Liang's corpse in the previous episode, he recovers his Golden Core for his new body. Since it's his own, he's able to merge it with his new body and he automatically becomes Late stage Core Formation again.
I've had my share of wounds,
now I want to fight back.
Is my destiny a wall of restrictions
that's blocking all my hopes
for life ?
My flesh and blood witnessed the past,
my adversity pushed me to brave the waves.
How do you navigate through the years passing by ?
Nirvana and rebirth are no longer
out of reach.
Immortals
are obsessed with delusions of grandeur.
Renegades
seek to crush the impermanence of the heavens.
Don't tell me that I overestimate myself
and that the path to revenge leads to hell
because I don't see the harm in that.
My new body opens its eyes
and awakens from its dream.
I have overcome many trials
to get this body back.
No matter how many endless dark nights go by,
I can still see.
By sticking to this thought, I will get it done
by my own hands.
Returning to my body opened my eyes,
I need to continue my Immortal journey.
With a flick of a finger,
only my indomitable heart remains.
Life and death trials temper me, I am not afraid of losing my soul.
Even if there are countless tribulations and hardships.
Overcome this fate, smash through the obstacles,
like the descent of a god.